[
    {
    "question":"Which of the following is the use of function in python?",
    "optionA":"Functions are reusable pieces of programs",
    "optionB":"you can't also create your own functions",
    "optionC":"Functions don't provide better modularity",
    "optionD":"All of the above",
    "answer":"Functions are reusable pieces of programs"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a feature of DocString?",
        "optionA": "Associating documentation with Python modules, functions, classes, and methods",
        "optionB": "All functions should have a docstring",
        "optionC": "Docstrings can be accessed by the _doc_ attribute on objects",
        "optionD": "All of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },

    {
        "question": "Select which true for python function ",
        "optionA": "Python function doesn't return anything",
        "optionB": "Python function can return multiple values",
        "optionC": "Python function can return only a single value",
        "optionD": "Python doesn't support nested function",
        "answer": "Python function can return multiple values"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is called when a function is defined inside a class?",
        "optionA": "class",
        "optionB": "function",
        "optionC": "method",
        "optionD": "module",
        "answer":  "method"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of the following items are present in function header?",
        "optionA": "function name",
        "optionB": "parameter list",
        "optionC": "return value",
        "optionD": "Both A and B",
        "answer": "Both A and B"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is a recursive function?",
        "optionA": "A function that calls other function. ",
        "optionB": "Both A and B",
        "optionC": "A function which calls itself.",
        "optionD": "None of the above",
        "answer": "A function which calls itself."
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of the following function headers is correct?",
        "optionA": "def fun(a=2, b=3, c)",
        "optionB": "def fun(a=2, b, c=3)",
        "optionC": "def fun(a, b=2, c=3)",
        "optionD": "def fun(a, b, c=3, d)",
        "answer": "def fun(a, b=2, c=3)"
    },

    {
        "question": "How is a function declared in Python?",
        "optionA": "def function function_name():",
        "optionB": "declare function function_name():",
        "optionC": "def  function_name():",
        "optionD": "declare function_name():",
        "answer": "def  function_name():"
    },
    

    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the use of id() function in python? ",
        "optionA": "id() returns the size of object.",
        "optionB": "Both A and B",
        "optionC": "id() returns the identity of the object.",
        "optionD": "None of the above",
        "answer":  "id() returns the identity of the object."
    },
    
    {
        "question": "If return statement is not used inside the function, the function will return:",
        "optionA": "None",
        "optionB": "0",
        "optionC": "Null",
        "optionD": "Arbitary value",
        "answer":  "None"
    }

  
]